# **BRYAN** WILSON

bryan@brianwithay.com

<u>brianwithay.com</u> (937) 716-7285

#### **ABOUT**

Quality Assurance Analyst with over three years of manual and automated testing experience and over four years of experience with data analysis and visualization. Bryan is skilled at each level of the project lifecycle, from requirements and objective planning to testing and reporting.

## **EDUCATION**

BS, Management Information Systems Wright State University

# **SKILLS**

**Advanced:** Manual Testing, Test Case Management, Business Analysis, Specification Writing, Data Analysis and Visualization, Requirements Documentation

Intermediate: Automated Testing, SEO Analysis, HTML/CSS, JS/Node.js, Java, Digital Ad Campaigns, Load Testing

# **TOOLS I'VE WORKED WITH**

Jira, Selenium, Java, Nightwatch.js, Katalon, Tableau, RapidMiner, NoSQL/ MySQL/MSSQL, Sitefinity, Wordpress, Postman, Google Analytics, Google Adwords and more.

References available upon request...

## **EMPLOYMENT**

## **QUALITY ASSURANCE ANALYST Marxent**

2018 - Present Miamisburg, OH

- Performed functional testing for VR/AR, WebGL, iOS and Android Applications
- · Created test scripts, test cases and managed test plans
- Performed 3D product inspection for VR/AR and application platforms
- Managed bug reporting and project planning systems and specifications

## **QUALITY ASSURANCE ENGINEER** Real Art Design Group

2016 - 2018 Dayton, OH

- Performed manual and automated testing for web, mobile, VR/AR and client
- Managed test cases, bug reporting/project planning systems and specifications
- Analyzed and visualized data for internal and client use
- Hands-on at all phases of project development including design and functional review

# WINDOWS ENTERPRISE SYSTEMS CO-OP Lexis Nexis

2015 - 2016 Miamisburg, OH

- Created IT service tools allowing level 2 service tasks to be automated
- Performed business analysis duties for a Windows Server 2003 upgrade project
- Performed QA testing on Citrix and HP Operations Manager upgrade projects
- Developed and maintained customer-facing support and Sharepoint site

## CERTIFICATIONS

Google Analytics - June 2016 - Present

Google Adwords - May 2018 - Present

Microsoft MTA - IT Infrastructure - August 2015 - Present

Microsoft MTA - Database - August 2015 - Present